(Sheldon:)Okay. Now, on this side,
(Sheldon:)I am closer to the exit
in case of emergency.
(Amy:)Great. That's your side.
(Sheldon:)No, but I'm also closer to
the entrance in case of attack.
Okay, I'll take that side.
(Sheldon:)Ah, then again, what are
the odds of someone attacking me?
(Amy:)Rising rapidly.
(Sheldon:)Now, this side offers me
proximity to the bathroom,
(Sheldon:)but I am closer to the window
(Sheldon:)where perverts
can watch me sleep.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Amy:)What if we do this?
(Sheldon:)I suppose that works.
(Penny:)Great.
(Sheldon:)Although now I'm kind of worried
(Sheldon:)someone's hiding
behind those drapes.
(Bernadette:)This is ridiculous.
(Bernadette:)The doctor knows what the baby
is, the ultrasound tech knows,
(Bernadette:)Raj knows,